So basically, since this is like this, I do this...
I don't understand a thing!
What do I do?
Our achievement tests are right around the corner!
What am I gonna do?!
Sometimes you just need to relax.
Hey, what are you doing?
Alan-sama! Perfect timing!
Here. This is for you.
It can't go out to market, but it's still edible.
Should you be doing this right before the test?
It'll be fine!
The test results have no influence with my doom flags.
Doom flags?
Uh... Never mind!
Catarina-sama and Alan-sama?
Why are they together during our study period?
Don't tell me—
No, that simply couldn't be.
I've done so much to squash any chance of that happening.
Still, I have to get between them!
Oh, Mary!
Would you like to study with me?
What?! You really want me to?
Yeah. I'm done working in the fields,
and I wasn't getting anywhere studying alone.
I will!
HameFura, I Reincarnated
into an
Otome Game
as a
Villainess
with only
destruction flags···
aimaina I my me datte guruguru mazetara
If you mix it round and round it becomes unclear
akogare no kyuu tenkai ni niau kamo ne
With an unexpected development, maybe it will look good
ren ai nara iza morase
If it's love, express it now
tobikiri no dessert
with wonderful desserts
amazuppai cho misu wa oyurushi asobase
An addictive sweet and sour mix, I'm sorry to have fun
mawaru uruwashiki koi moyou
Love is a spiral pattern that spins on and on
chotto souzou naname you he massugu susume
I need to stop and think before moving forward
otome no route wa hitotsu janai
A maiden's route is not just one!
hatto suru lucky na ima ni gokigen you
My heart feels surprisingly lucky now
itsudatte maemukina desu
And so I will remain optimistic
ai mo kawarazu ni touhonseisou kou kando wo agete
If you want to win the game of love, you have to risk it all
kiyoku tadashiku utsukushiku are to wa yoku itta monda na
It's a pure, intense and beautiful feeling, so fight for it
kitto warui happy na mirai ni gokigen you
I still don't know if my ending will be happy or not
itsu datte maemukina desu
But I will remain optimistic
Episode 8
I Became Engulfed by Desire...
I can't believe Lady Catarina
asked me to study with her.
And she's sitting so close to me!
Mary...
I don't know how to do this one.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I don't know how to do that one, either.
Maybe we should ask the president, then.
And that's how you arrive at the answer.
Oh, I get it!
I understand now. You're a great teacher, President Sirius.
There are several reference books
on this in the east building's library.
They're available to borrow, so maybe you should go there.
We'll do that, President. Thank you!
I'm honored that I could be of help.
The library in the east building...
I've never been there before.
Neither have I.
I guess it's differentfrom the usual library.
Hello.
Where are you two headed?
Geordo-sama, how do you do?
We're on our way to the library in the east building.
That's perfect.
I was thinking of going there myself.
May I join you?
Of course.
Mary, do you take issue with that?
N-Not at all. Please, do accompany us.
Just when I thought I'd get some
time alone with Lady Catarina...
Sister, where are you off to?
The library.
Oh? Maybe I'll come with you.
The library? What a coincidence.
I'm going there, too.
I'll join you, too!
Oh! I'd love to join you!
Everyone ended up joining us...
Darn it all!
Please, Catarina-sama, have a seat right here.
I'll sit next to you.
I-I'm sorry! I guess I'm a little hungry...
Shall I go and get some sweets?
Thanks, Maria!
I-I'll help you.
I'll bring the best tea you've ever had.
Thanks, Mary!
Just leave it to me!
It all looks like sweets!
Did this just shine for a second?
What's going on?!
I-It's so bright...
What is that light?
Did you see that?
Yes...
They all just disappeared...
...into the book?
This is ancient script.
It says... "A Tale by the Name of..."
..."Desire"?
"When one's desire is fulfilled..."
"...those captured may be saved."
Let's try and read it.
Right.
Catarina-sama?!
Catarina-sama!
Is this...
the world within the book?
It looks like we can't interfere
with the world in the book.
What in the world is going on?
Come, this way.
Why am I dressed like this?
I was just in the library a moment ago...
Well, now that the wedding is over,
you finally belong to me alone.
Wedding?
So this is a wedding dress?!
No one will be coming here
for the rest of the night.
You'll be alone with me until morning.
What?! I can't do that!
I have to study for my test!
Your face couldn't possibly look any cuter.
It makes me want to make
you even more uncomfortable.
U-Um... Geordo-sama?
Shall I start by taking those lips of yours?
H-Honestly, I'd prefer
some sweets over wine...
Wh-What in the world is going on here?!
I can't bear to see any more!
Geordo-sama, what do you think
you're doing to my Catarina-sama?!
Was that an illusion the book
was showing us?
Or is it really happening inside the book?
Whether it's real or an illusion,
I won't stand for it!
What can I do to rescue Catarina-sama?
Let's open the book one more time.
Sister, wake up.
Keith...
Come on, pick up your pen
and face your desk.
Huh? I'm suddenly back in my own room?
Wh-What is this?
Keith is acting weird today!
And he's giving off an oddly sexy vibe...
You'd better get your studying done...
or I'll eat this.
My sweets! Give that to me!
Then... open wide.
Huh?!
"Ah..."
Ah...
No!
I absolutely, positively won't
let anyone feed Catarina-sama!
It was a story about Keith-sama
and Catarina-sama this time...
"A Tale by the Name of Desire"...
So that was Geordo-sama's
desire we saw before,
and this was Keith-sama's desire?
Huh?!
Come to think of it, I do remember hearing
that somewhere in this school,
there's a magic book that craves the desires of humans.
I've heard that before, too.
It was one of this school's seven mysteries.
This book was written long before
this school was established,
but it looks like a brand new book...
and that's because it prolongs its
life by feeding on human desires
as its energy source.
Hey! What do we have to do
to get them all out of you?!
Tell me!
Mary-sama, please, calm down!
In the preface, it says,
"When one's desire is fulfilled, those captured may be saved."
So if the desire of one of the people in it is fulfilled,
they would all be able to return here, right?
You mean they all have to live out their desires in full?
Wait!
They all love Catarina-sama,
which means their desires would be...
to do all kinds of things to Catarina-sama?!
No way!
Well, we need to open the book, or nothing will...
No! I don't want to see any of that!
But if we don't, they'll all be trapped in the book forever!
I know, but...
It's all right, Mary-sama.
I'm here with you.
We may be in a bad situation,
but let's work together
to find the best way to fix it.
Maria-san...
Catarina-sama, I've found another interesting book.
Wow, all of these look interesting!
Wait... huh?
Why am I in your personal library?
Don't you like it?
Oh, I do!
All the books in here
are books I'd love to read!
I wish I could live here!
Catarina-sama... O-Of course!
I'm prepared...
to start living with you at any time!
S-Sophia?
Because, Catarina-sama, I...
l-lo... lo...
I love you, too, Sophia!
You mean it?!
How much?! Which do you love more, me or sweets?!
Huh? W-Well, of course, I...
I can't believe Sophia-sama slammed
Catarina-sama against a wall!
She even told her she l-loved her...
The next one! Let's try the next one!
What's all this? Where am I this time?
May I have this dance?
Who are you?
Black hair, black eyes...
And the way he's dressed...
Is this... the Devilish Count?
Nicol?!
It's Nicol-sama!
Nicol-sama!
What now?
We're saved!
Um, Nicol-sama, which way is the school?
I need to get back to the library.
I'm hungry, too.
I don't want to let you go.
I want to keep you...
trapped in these arms forever.
Let's burn this book!
Mary-sama, please calm down!
Are these things really what they're all thinking?!
It may be that the magic is making
their desires rage out of control!
We still have to see more?!
Wasn't that enough?!
It looks like that wasn't enough.
If that's what it wants...
I'll face down this desire
or whatever else it wants me to!
Mary-sama?
After all this, I don't even need to read it.
I can guess what's going to happen.
This is just awful...
But the one it's hurting the most is Catarina-sama.
She left all these sweets here, untouched.
And I'm sure she must
be quite hungry by now...
That's it!
None of the stories we've seen so far
have been about Catarina-sama's desire.
Yes, you're right.
"When one's desire is fulfilled, those captured may be saved."
So if Catarina-sama's desire is fulfilled...
They'll all be set free!
We'll just have to stake all our hopes on that!
I'm so hungry.
How do I get back to the library?
I want to eat Maria's sweets!
I want to drink Mary's tea!
Catarina-sama, the sweets are right here!
And so is the tea!
It's a pity we can't bring them to her.
Sweets!
Wow! The whole thing is made of sweets!
Yum!
This is great!
Incredible!
I can still eat more!
I can eat all I want!
Strange...
No matter how much I eat, it's not enough.
I want more! More, more!
More! More! More! More! More! More! More! More! More!
More! More! More!
Wh-What's happening?
Something is clearly wrong!
We should close the book!
Is everyone all right?
Yeah...
Ow...
More... More... More... More...
Yummy...
Catarina-sama!
Mary?
Um, so you're saying...
...this book, which is one
of the school's seven mysteries...
...sucked us up and trapped us inside?
Yes.
Oh, so it's a magic book!
No wonder all those weird
things kept happening.
Tales of desire?
Desire...
Desire... is most definitely what that was.
Uh, I need to get going.
I must go, as well.
Me, too.
You all seem awfully embarrassed
now that you're back in the real world.
Embarrassed? What do you mean?
What happened inside that book?
All I did was play the piano.
And that's all you need to know, Alan-sama.
Anyway, this book looked as though it
were in pain at the end of all that.
This just occurred to me...
The world inside the book
is fictional, right?
So no matter how many sweets
Catarina-sama ate, she'd never feel full.
How strange!
I keep eating and eating,
but it's not enough!
I think Catarina-sama's desire
just kept growing bigger,
until the book couldn't contain it anymore.
I see!
So does that mean Catarina-sama
is stronger than the book's magic?
Yes!
That's my Catarina-sama!
This is bliss!
kokoro ga tsukiru made moyase
My heart yearns for you so much
kantan ni clear dekiru
I thought it was easy to clear
koi wa game sou omotteta
To win at this love game
gururi madowasete hikiyosete
I'm spinning around and pulling you in
otosu shudai wo narabuke wo
Following along in my footsteps
naze kimi dakara igai
Why are you so captivating?
dono route erabeba saita nano ka
Which route will be the best choice?
kotae wa mienai
I can't find the answer
Bad End no unmei demo boku no mono ni nareba ii
Even if fate leads me to a "Bad End", it's fine
sou saa douse hametsu suru no nara kimi to
You're the one I want in my life
zettai ni zetsumei shinai aida to chikaukara
My love for you will never change
ubai saa nareru kakugo
Prepare to be conquered
mubou mi de muteki nayosashisa mudai makichirasu mae ni
You make me feel invincible, imprudent and happy at the same time
sono chisen wo hitorijime shitte miseru
I want to find out more about you
donna kodoku mo itami mo
No matter how much the pain is
kimi goto uketomeru
I will carry it for you
machi ukeru zetsubou mo nozomu tokoro
Even if despair awaits me, I'll take it on
Oh, darn it!
I just can't resist!
Standing on grass just feels so good!
You're barefoot?!
You know...
that's not something a noble lady should do.
Aw, but it feels really nice.
You should try it, too.
Wow, that does feel nice.
Hey, Catarina?
Hey!
Up here!
Why are you climbing a tree again?
You're not a child!
It's been so long since I climbed
one, so I wanted to try it.
Why don't you join me, Alan-sama?
The view from up here is really pretty!
Seriously... What am I going to do with you?
Welcome!
I had forgotten...
Just seeing it from a different spot
makes the world look so different.
Pretty, isn't it?
Y-Yeah...
I wish time would stop right now.
Catarina-sama?
Where could she be?
Alan-sama?!
Is this another tale of desire?
No, it's not!
This is the real world!
Don't! Don't even think about it!
I have to get between them!